嘿 老爸 那最后一片培根你还吃吗
Hey, dad, you gonna eat your last piece of bacon?
有意思
Nice.
噢 对了 老爸 学校正在开展职业日
Oh, dad, by the way I'm having career day at my school,
不知道你有兴趣参加吗
And I was wondering if you could come.
真的吗 你想让我去谈谈我的工作吗
Really? You want me to come in and talk about my job?
-太好了 -大块头 别激动
- That's fantastic. - Easy, big guy.
你只是个打酱油的 仅此而已
You're a time filler. Nothing more, nothing less.
的确不那么好了
That's a little less fantastic.
嘿 我怎么没参加过你的职业日
Hey, how come I never came in and spoke to one of your classes?
我们当年没有职业日
We didn't have career day back then.
这是最近才兴起的
It's a whole new idea.
是吗 我当年就有职业日啊
Really? They had career day when I was a kid.
肯定中间停办了一代的时间
Must have skipped a generation.
嘿 盖比
Hey, Gabe.
为什么你不邀请我去啊
Why aren't you asking me to career day this year?
因为去年所发生的惨案
Because of what happened last year.
我们来看一看在急诊室发生的趣事
We see a lot of interesting things in the emergency room.
这就是你在电锯上不按指示行事后
This is what can happen when you don't follow the directions.
的下场
On the chainsaw.
孩子们 孩子们 把你们的尖叫留到最后
Kids, kids, hold your reactions till the end.
我们还有很多图片要看呢
We've got a lot of pictures here.
难道现在连断肢都对十一岁的儿童不宜吗
So now severed limbs are off-limits to 11-year-olds?
搞什么啊
What?
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第二十八集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E28  Story Time
”那个伤心的小匹萨 起司说道“
"'And cheesy, ' the sad little pizza said,"
“我感觉自己太平庸了”
'I just feel so plain.'
他的好朋友腊肠匹萨 胡椒说道
And pepe, his friend the pepperoni pizza said,
“不要这么想 起司 这正是孩子们喜欢你的地方”
'but, cheesy, that's why kids love you.'
然后起司感觉好多了
And cheesy felt all better.
“剧终”
"The end."
老妈
Mom.
坎蒂丝 你讲的故事太好了 我们很喜欢
Candace, thank you so much for this story, we really enjoyed it..
我听见你打呼噜了
I heard you snoring.
最重要的是查莉喜欢 对吧 查莉
The important thing is Charlie liked, right Charlie?
不 妈咪
No, mommy.
她没说错 的确不是一本好书
She's right. It was not a good book.
我都可以写个更出色的故事
I could write a better story than that.
我希望你没有吹牛 我在儿童出版社工作
I wish you would. I working in children's Publishing
而我一直致力于寻找才华横溢的人
And I am always on the look out for new talent.
先不说了 咱们下周见
Anyway, we'll see you guys next week.
-再见 坎蒂丝 -再见
- Bye, Candace. - See ya.
-一语惊醒梦中人 -我也是
- That gives me an idea. - Me too.
我应该写本儿童读物
I should write a children's book!
关于写作你了解多少
What do you know about writing?
关于孩子你又了解多少
What do you know about children?
不如咱们双剑合璧
Maybe we could write a book together.
然后我们就可以在下周的故事时间读给大家听
And then we could read it at next week's story time.
孩子们将爱死我们的故事 而坎蒂丝将会出版成书
And the kids will go crazy. Candace will publish it,
我就可以成为《早安 丹佛》里的新闻
And I'll be on "good morning Denver."
现在就让我们把精力放在给孩子写故事上吧
Right now let's just focus on writing a good story for the kids.
没错 没错 没错 孩子才是最重要的
You're right. You're right. It's all about the kids.
噢 太好了 晚餐到了
Oh, great. I guess dinner's here.
这里是咕唧炸鸡向您的问候
And a happy kwikki chikki hello to you.
-我听见了 斯科特 -我知道你听见了 但当我想让你
- I heard that, Scott. - I'm sure that you heard, but when I ask.
做顿家常菜时 你却突然失聪了
For a home-cooked meal, you suddenly go deaf.
我不是家庭主妇 我也有工作
I'm not a housewife. I work too.
用不用我一会儿再来
Do you want me to come back later?
不用 不然晚餐会变凉的
No, then the food will be cold.
不用担心 已经凉了
Don't worry. It's already cold.
让我们问问这哥们 你是怎么看的
Let's ask this guy. What do you think?
拜托了 我们需要你的观点
Come on, we want your opinion.
谁应该负责晚饭
Who is responsible for dinner?
这个问题有点儿棘手 我父母也遇到过这个问题
That is a tough question. I've seen my parents have the very same argument
因为他们也都有工作
'cause they both have jobs too.
-怎么解决的呢 -大吵
- How do they work it out? - Very loudly.
但是最后他们好好谈了谈
But at least they're communicating,
也许你们也需要好好谈谈
Which is maybe what you guys need to do.
我们不是正在谈吗
But we are communicating.
真的吗 确定一定以及肯定吗
Are you? Are you really?
没有 我们没有
No, we're not.
不如从现在开始吧
Maybe it's time to start.
我只想回到我们刚结婚时的生活
I just want things to go back to the way they were when we first got married.
我也是 对不起 亲爱的
I want that too. I'm sorry, honey.
我也对不起
I'm sorry too.
好了 现在只剩下一句话了
Well, I guess there's only one thing left to say.
一共十四块九毛五
That'll be $14.95.
好了 你听听这个怎么样
Okay, tell me what you think of this.
“演员 歌手 舞蹈家 喜剧演员 艺人 护士”
"actress, singer, dancer, comedian, entertainer, nurse,"
妻子 四个崽儿的母亲 如今艾米·邓肯又将把作者
Wife, mother of four, Amy Duncan now adds author.
“加入到她的人生角色清单中”
"To her long list of credits."
搞什么
What is that?
书皮上的个人简历
It's my bio for the book jacket.
太长了吗
Too long?
我可以省去 “妻子和四个崽儿的母亲”
'cause I could lose "wife and mother of four."
嘿 不如这样吧
Hey, I have an idea.
别管书皮了 咱先写本书吧
Instead of a book jacket, let's write a book.
好吧 感觉有点儿拖我后腿 不过没事 来吧
Okay, seems kind of backwards to me, but okay, sure.
咱俩一起集思广益 看看怎么样
Let's just brainstorm and see what we come up with.
好主意
Excellent idea.
头脑风暴
Brainstorming.
风暴头脑
Stormy brain.
思考 思想 想法 话语
Thinking, thoughts, ideas, words...
老妈 头脑风暴通常很安静
Mom, brainstorms are usually quiet.
抱歉
Sorry.
记住 点子可以来自任何地方
And remember, an idea can come from anywhere.
-有了 -什么
- Got it! - What?
拉拉
Trashy.
Trashy?
垃圾桶拉拉
Trashy the trash can.
我刚才盯着垃圾桶 于是就想到了
I was staring at the trash can and it just came to me.
好吧 拉拉
Okay, trashy.
有什么故事可讲
So what's his story?
泰迪 我又不能做全部工作 是我想到了拉拉
Teddy, I can't do all the work. I came up with trashy.
好吧 那么孩子们能从中学到什么呢
Yeah, but what's he trying to teach the kids?
噢 这个嘛
Oh, okay.
这个 当拉拉
Um, well, when trashy.
看到了某人乱扔垃圾
Sees someone litter,
他说 “诶 诶 诶 诶”
He says, "enh-enh-enh-enh."
我太有才了 我应该为其电影版配音
I do that really well. I should do hjs voice for the movie.
嘿 老妈 不如换个其他的想法吧
Hey, mom, let's think of some other ideas.
你确定吗
Really?
因为我觉着我的题材还不错
'cause I'm loving me some trashy.
成了 成了 不如我们分开工作
Okay okay, well, maybe we should work separately,
然后明天把各自想出的点子进行汇总
Then get together tomorrow with some new ideas.
千万不要看到什么就写什么
That aren't based off of the first thing you looked at.
-好吧 -很好
- Fine. - Good.
-我无所谓 -很好
- Whatever. - Great.
诶 诶 诶
Enh-enh-enh.
我可以把它印在T恤上
I can see it on a t-shirt.
好了 老爸 明天就是职业日了
Okay, dad, career day is tomorrow.
你的计划如何了
What's your plan?
-我的计划 -是啊
- My plan? - Yeah.
即兴发挥
To wing it.
老爸啊 这不是你和我妈结婚纪念日上的祝酒词
Dad, this isn't a toast to mom on your anniversary.
这很重要
This is important.
你不能站起来就讲你的工作
Now you can't just get up there and talk aboutour job.
你必须表演个节目
You gotta put on a show.
你要赢得的是欢呼声 而不是牛排
This is all about the sizzle, not the steak.
明白了
I get it.
你想让我带去几只小动物过去
You want me to bring in a couple of critters that I caught,
比如老鼠 负鼠
Like a rat or a possum.
你能抓到更牛的动物吗
Is there any chance you could catch something exciting,
比如短吻鳄啊 狮子啊
Like an alligator or a lion.
或者北极熊 这个好
Or a polar bear? Yeah.
这个嘛 鉴于明天就是职业日了 可能有些困难
Well, those might be tough since career day is tomorrow.
况且我们住在丹佛
And we live in Denver.
好了 老爸 不管你怎么做
All right, dad, whatever you do,
别给我丢脸就成
Just don't embarrass me.
指的就是把衣服塞到裤子里 再换上一条最结实的皮带
That means shirt tucked in and your most dependable belt.
嘿 那种事情不会再发生了
Hey, that's not gonna happen again.
天啊 我还真给孩子留下阴影了
Man, you ruin one little league game...
又是我
Hi again.
噢 什么东西这么好闻
Ooh, something smells good.
-我在做排骨 -那你为什么还订炸鸡
- I'm making pork chops. - Then why'd you order chicken?
其实 我们希望你可以帮我们解决另一个问题
Actually, we were hoping you could help us with another problem.
噢 好吧 出来吧
Oh, well, come on out.
请坐 不要拘束
Have a seat, make yourselves at home.
和我说说吧
Talk to me.
情况就是 克里斯汀的母亲想搬来和我们一起住
The thing is Christine's mother wants to come and stay with us.
住两个星期
For two weeks.
我本来想让她少住几天
I wanted to ask her to come for less time,
但是
But...
但是什么
But what?
别害怕 告诉炸鸡兄
Come on, tell the chicken guy.
-我怕她 好了 我说了 -没错 但因为
- But I'm afraid of her. There, I said it. - Yeah, but just because...
别急 我们先帮助克里斯汀
Hold on. We're working with Christine now.
现在 克里斯汀 给你感受如何
Now, Christine, how did that make you feel?
我感觉 很难过 而且我希望斯科特
Well, it makes me feel sad, and I want Scott...
-斯科特 你说吧 -我感觉我想帮克里斯汀
- Scott, feedback. - I feel that I'd like to help Christine,
让她不再伤心 -你怎么帮
- So she wouldn't be so sad.- How can you help?
那个 但你问我
Well... but you asked me.
别质疑我的方法
Don't question my process.
我来告诉你怎么帮 去约会
I'll tell you how you can help. Date night.
-约会 -没错 当你的母亲来这里住时
- Date night. - Yeah, make sure you guys schedule some alone time.
去享受下二人世界
While your mother's here.
你们的需求也很重要啊
Your needs are important too.
-去约会 真是个好主意 -是啊 太谢谢你了
- Date night. That's a great idea. - Yeah. Thank you so much.
嘿 这是我应该的
Hey, it's what I do.
现在让我们去看看排骨怎么样了
Now let's take a look at those pork chops.
现在在我们分享点子之前
Now before we share our book ideas,
请记住要友善
Let's remember to be kind.
没错 点子全是好点子
That's right. There are no bad ideas.
我先来
I'll go first.
请看
Ba-bam!
嘿 拉拉卷土重来了
Hey, trashy's back.
可不是吗
I know.
我费尽脑汁 但就是无法超越这个金点子
Try as I might, I could not top him.
现在能说说我的点子吗
Can I share one of my ideas now?
好 当然可以 来吧
Y-yeah, of course. Go ahead.
好的
Okay.
我的点子是一个故事
So my idea is a story.
关于一个罐头 名叫
About a little tin can and his name is...
“蒂姆罐”
"Tim can."
故事的开始是蒂姆在商店的货架上
So the story begins with Tim on the shelf at the store.
然后他经历了一系列的冒险之旅
Then he goes on some amazing adventures.
可以教给孩子们循环利用 你觉得怎么样
That teach kids all about recycling. What do you think?
我觉得我之前说错了
I think I was wrong.
这里不全是好点子
There are bad ideas.
闺女啊 请不要自责
Honey, don't get too down on yourself.
我把拉拉这个标准设的有点高
I set the bar pretty high with trashy.
你没开玩笑吧 你只是 你指着一个垃圾箱
Are you kidding? You just... you pointed at a trash can.
然后就起了个破名字 我也可以啊
And gave it a stupid name. I could do that.
不如写个故事是关于桌子桌桌或者搅拌器搅搅
Let's write a story about tabley or blendery.
搅拌器搅搅 成了 这个太没水平了
Blendery? Okay, that's just silly.
搅拌器能说啥呢  “搅 搅 搅” 吗
What would a blender say? "chop chop chop"?
连我都不能在上面做文章
Even I can't make that work.
知道还有什么做不了文章吗 这个
You know what doesn't work? This.
你知道你这是什么吗 羡慕嫉妒恨
You know what you are... jealous.
是啊 被你说中了
Yes, I am,
羡慕嫉妒恨那些不用和你一起工作的人们
Of people that don't have to work with you.
那好吧 那就别和我一起工作
Then fine. Don't work with me.
我自己写我的“拉拉”
I'll write "trashy" by myself.
好啊 那我也自己写我的“蒂姆罐”
Okay, well, I'll write "tim can" by myself,
到下周的故事时间 让孩子们来决定谁的故事最好
Then next week at story time, we'll let the kids decide which one's best.
没错 没错 他们会决定把你的书扔进垃圾桶
Oh yeah yeah. They'll decide... To feed your book to trashy!
当妈咪我的故事时间读完书后
When mommy finishes reading her book at story time,
你要跳起来大叫“耶 拉拉”
I want you to jump up and yell, "yay, trashy!"
-你可以办到吗 -耶 拉拉
- Can you do that for me? - Yay, trashy!
耶
Yay!
-你搞什么呢 -没什么
- What are you doing? - Nothing.
你这是在买通查莉 你这是在作弊
You're coaching Charlie. Mom, that's cheating.
我是她妈
I am her mother.
教会她应该喜欢什么东西是我的责任
It is my job to tell her what stuff to like.
是吗 那拉拉是好东西吗
Okay, so trashy's the right stuff?
诶 诶 诶
Enh-enh-enh.
即使你在嘲笑我
Even though you're mocking me,
也掩盖不了光芒
It still works.
好了 查莉 重复我说的
Okay, Charlie, now repeat after me,
“蒂姆罐 我爱蒂姆罐”
"Tim can, I love Tim can."
耶 拉拉
Yay, trashy!
可恶
Gahhh!
你们 你们怎么来了
Guys, what are you doing here?
-这位是我妈妈伊莱恩 -我们需要你
- This is my mother Elaine. - We need you.
我们曾订过炸鸡
We tried ordering chicken,
但他们说你今天休息
But they said you weren't working today.
那好吧 那我就帮帮你们
Well, I guess I could fit you in.
请坐
Have a seat.
好了 和我说说吧
Okay, talk to me.
我大老远的穿越整个国家
I didn't come halfway across this country.
结果这两个人去约会了
So these two could go out on a date night.
不爽你就走啊
Then feel free to go back.
斯科特 这是我妈
Scott, that is my mother.
好了 好了 我了解事情的来龙去脉了
Okay okay, I see what's going on here.
你们两个在说着对方 但不是和对方说
You guys are talking at each other, not with each other.
现在你和我说 我再和他说
Now you talk to me, and I'll talk to him.
你再和我说 我再和她说
And he'll talk to me and I'll talk to her.
她再和我说 我再和你说
She'll talk to me, and I'll talk to you.
也就是你对我 我对他 他对我
That's you to me, me to him, him to me,
我对她 她对我 我对你
Me to her, her to me, me to you.
就这么简单
It's just that simple.
看来你没戴那顶帽子 谈话效果骤减啊
It's kind of hard to take you seriously without the hat.
噢 我的错
Oh, sorry.
回归正题吧
Let's get to work.
我好怕失去你啊
I was just afraid of losing you.
你不会失去我的
You'll never lose me.
你愿意待多长时间就待多长时间 妈妈
And you can stay here as long as you like, mom.
这里是什么情况
What's going on in here?
治愈心灵 你所看到的一切就是心灵的治愈
Healing. What's going on in here is healing.
谢谢 特透鲍姆先生 噢
Thank you, Mr. Turtlebaum. Oh.
“双特透鲍姆会计师事务所
Of "turtlebaum & turtlebaum accounting:
一个专业的公司”
A professional corporation."
好了 现在用温暖六号房的掌声欢迎
Right. Now let's give a warm room six welcome.
我的爸爸 鲍伯·邓肯
To my dad, Bob Duncan.
-嘿 -为我争光
- Hey. - Dazzle me.
嘿 大家好 我是鲍伯·邓肯 鲍伯到 害虫跑
Hey, everybody, I am Bob Duncan of Bob's bugs be gone.
我今天来到这里
And I am here today.
是给你们说说
To talk to you.
害虫防治的艺术
About the fine art of pest control.
好了 在我的日常生活中
Yes. Now in my typical day,
我见过各种昆虫
I come across all sorts of insects...
蚂蚁 蟑螂 老鼠
Ants, roaches, mice.
你们应该说 “等一下 邓肯先生”
"wait, Mr. Duncan," you say,
“老鼠不是昆虫 它们是”
"mice aren't insects. They are..."
有人知道吗
Anybody?
说对了 它们是啮齿动物
That's right. They are rodents.
我们不是来学习的
Not here to learn.
总之 我带来了一些动物
Anyway, I've brought along some animals.
这些动物 虽然是我在工作中无法遇到的
That, although I've never seen them on the job,
我也许可以将它们抓住
I could quite possibly catch.
如果我们生活在其他气候带中
If we were living in a different climate.
在其他大洲上
On a different continent.
比如
For example...
看看这东西
Look at that guy
是一只帝王蝎
That is an emperor scorpion.
有的人说被它叮一下比被蜜蜂蛰一下要致命
Now some people say that its sting is no worse than a bee's,
其他人呢 其实 他们都不敢在旁边吱声
And others, well, they're not around to say anything.
嗷
Ow!
我开玩笑的 我开玩笑的
I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding.
嘿 你们认为那就很牛了 是不是
Hey, you thought that was cool, huh?
看了这东西后你们才知道什么才是牛
Wait until you check out this guy.
哇
Whoa.
快看看
Look at him, huh?
这是一条玉米蛇
This is a corn snake.
精彩吧 是不是 台上的是我老爸
Pretty cool, huh? That's my dad.
大家好 欢迎来到读书时间
Hello, everybody, welcome to story time.
我叫泰迪 今天会和以往不同
My name is Teddy, and today we have a special treat.
因为你们将听到两个故事
You're gonna hear two stories.
第一个是我编写的 名字叫
The first one is written by me, and it's called.
《蒂姆罐和他的冒险之旅》
"Tim can and his amazing journey."
是罐头吗
Tin can?
蒂姆 蒂姆罐
Tim. Tim can.
好了 在我们开始之前
All right, now before we begin,
顺便说一下 截止今日
Just a reminder, as of today,
这个故事还未被发表过
This story has not been published.
开始了 “很久以前 有一个盛汤的小罐子”
Okay. "Once upon a time, there was a little can of soup.
他就叫蒂姆
And his name was Tim.
蒂姆就在一家杂货店里 盼望着有朝一日能有人将它买走
Tim lived at the grocery store hoping someday someone would buy him.
有一天 一位漂亮的女士买下了他
One day a nice woman did.
“那位女士就叫坎蒂丝”
"Her name was Candace."
噢 嘿 你也叫这个名字
Oh! Hey! That's your name.
太巧了 继续吧
-That's funny. -Okay.
“坎蒂丝把他带回了家”
"Candace took Tim home,"
把他的汤倒进了锅里
Poured his soup in a pot,
如何把他扔进了回收箱里
Then tossed him in the recycling bin.
“蒂姆很伤心 ‘难道就这样了吗’ 他疑惑着”
"Tim was sad. 'Is that all there is? ' he wondered."
我也疑惑着呢
That's what I'm wondering.
可怜的水管工 不得不跟随着我
Poor plumber, having to follow me.
必须要有人接替猫王的旗帜 对吧
I guess somebody had to go on after Elvis, right?
干得不错 老爸 更值得一提的是
You did great, dad, and more importantly,
-皮带同样给力 -是啊
- So did your belt. - Yeah.
盖比啊 你老爹不会让你失望的
Gabe, your old man wasn't gonna let you down.
你看见那只蝎子了吗
Have you seen the scorpion?
-什么 你把蝎子弄 -等等 等等
- What? You lost a scorp... - Wait wait wait wait.
让咱爷俩安静的将它找到
Let's just find it quietly by ourselves.
好吧 蝎子没读 是吧
All right. Scorpions aren't poisonous, right?
我怎么知道 我今天早上刚租过来的
How should I know? I just rented it this morning.
我记得电视上说过蝎子可以让你瘫痪
I thought I saw something on tv that said a scorpion can paralyze you.
谢谢你的提醒
That might have been a nice thing to mention.
在它爬到我身上之前
Before I let it walk on me.
他们好像找到了
I think they found it.
“在蒂姆被回收利用成为蒂姆馅饼盘子”
"and after Tim had been recycled into Tim pie plate."
和铝箔后
And Tim aluminum foil,
他又变成了蒂姆罐
He went back to being Tim can.
“从此过上了幸福快乐的生活 剧终”
"And lived happily ever after. The end."
耶
Yay!
好了 孩子们 是不是比《起司和胡椒匹萨》好上百倍啊
Well, kids, wasn't that better than "cheesy and pepe pizza"?
是
Yeah!
嘿 孩子们 拉拉来也
Hey, kids, here comes trashy!
嘿 大家好
Hey, everybody,
我是垃圾桶拉拉
I'm trashy the trash can.
但我不是普通的垃圾桶
But I'm not just any trash can.
不是的 我是一个能够分发糖果的垃圾桶
No, I'm a trash can that gives out candy.
呜
Whoo!
垃圾桶最精彩的部分
And the best part about trashy.
是他的魔法
Is that he has magical powers.
他有无穷无尽的糖果
So that he never runs out of candy.
来吧 使劲吃吧 来吧 吃吧
Yeah, eat it up. Yeah, eat it up.
这就是垃圾桶拉拉的故事 剧终
And that's the story of trashy the trash can. The end.
这不是个故事
That's not a story.
你这是利用糖果来买通孩子们对你书的好感
You're just throwing candy at the kids so they'll like your book better.
好吧 看看效果 谁认为拉拉比蒂姆罐好
Well, let's see if it works. Who likes trashy better than Tim can?
-我 -噢 噢 噢 好的 很好
- Me! - Ooh ooh ooh! Yeah yeah!
噢 真的吗
Mm-hmm. - Oh, yeah?
听好了 我忘了告诉你们一个关于蒂姆罐的事情
Well, I forgot to tell you one thing about Tim can.
他会带你们大家去图书馆
He is gonna take all of you kids in the library.
去吃冰激凌
Out for ice cream.
好了 大家跟我喊
Okay, everybody repeat after me.
拉拉 拉拉 拉拉
Trashy! Trashy! Trashy!
-蒂姆罐 蒂姆罐 -拉拉 拉拉
- Tim can! Tim can! Tim can! - Trashy! Trashy! Trashy!
噢 坎蒂丝 你想买我的故事吗
Oh, Candace, do you wanna buy my story?
还是想买我的故事
Or do you wanna buy story?
我想的是找一个新的图书馆来继续故事时间
What I want is to find a new library for story time.
这下好了 五百件这东西要我怎么处理
Great. What am I supposed to do with 500 of these?
今晚又出现什么问题了
And what seems to be the problem tonight?
没问题 事情一切顺利
There's no problem. Everything's great.
别玩这套了 直入主题吧
Aren't we past this? Let's dive in.
没问题 真的 我很好得很
No, seriously, we're fine.
我们解决了所有问题
We worked out all our issues.
那你们为什么还订炸鸡
Then why'd you order chicken?
因为我们饿了
Because we're hungry.
如果你们没有矛盾了
But if you guys are fine,
那我只是一个普通送外卖的了
Then I'm just the chicken guy.
差不多吧
Pretty much.
谢谢
Thanks.
不用找了
Keep the change.
我还会回来的
I'll be back!
我忘了拿辅料了
I forgot your sides.
盖比
Gabe.
能和你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you for a minute?
我忙着吃奶酪条呢
Kinda busy with my string cheese.
儿子 今天真是对不住了
Buddy, I'm really sorry about today.
你只要求我别给你丢人
All you asked me to do was not embarrass you.
但我还是丢了
And that's exactly what I did.
老爸 你没给我丢人
Dad, you didn't embarrass me.
对亏了你 现在大家都追捧我
Thanks to you, everybody loves me.
什么
What?
真的 你被蝎子蛰后 就晕过去了
Yeah, after the scorpion stung you, and then you passed out,
然后特透鲍姆先生想从你的体内吸出毒素
And then Mr. Turtlebaum tried to suck the poison out of you.
结果他又不省人事了
And then he passed out.
什么
What?
趁混乱之中 蛇又爬了出去
In all the confusion, the snake got loose.
好吧 先不谈这个 特透鲍姆做了什么
Yeah, backup. Turtlebaum did what?
当你在医院的时候
And then while you were at the hospital,
消防队来了 整个学校的人都被疏散了
The fire department came and the whole school was evacuated for the day.
我是站在你肩膀上的巨人
I am a hero because of you.
谢了 老爸
Thanks, dad.
请正面回答我那个特透鲍姆问题
Now I'm gonna need an answer on that turtlebaum question.
好了 查莉 无需此言
Well, Charlie, needless to say,
我的故事没发表
I'm still unpublished,
但是好消息是 老妈也没得逞
But the good news is so is mom.
我认为我们学到了一件很重要的事情
I think we learned a very important lesson.
即便我穿着垃圾桶 魅力也不减
I look good even in a trash can.
好吧 算是一个教训吧
Well, that's one of the lessons.
-所以 -我感觉好空虚
- So... - I just feel so empty,
感觉被抛弃了
So abandoned.
更准确的来说 我感觉被利用了
I guess it'd be safe to say I feel used.
你明白我的意思吗
You know what I'm saying?
PJ 这可怜的娃在这儿都十分钟了
PJ, the poor kid been here for 10 minutes.
快付给他钱吧
Pay him already.
嘿 明天你还来吗
Hey, see you tomorrow?
有时候 无需多言 除了祝你好运啊 查莉
Sometimes there's nothing left to say but good luck, Charlie.
可怜的我啊
Poor me.
我没有任何的辅料
I don't have any toppings,
只有奶酪
Just cheese.
你个废柴 起司
You're a loser, cheesy.
瞅瞅我 满身的香肠啊
Look at me, all covered in pepperoni.
我认为有时候普普通通也会有好处的
There must be something good about being so plain.
噢 是吗 当你想到了 记得告诉我
Oh yeah, when you think of it, let me know.
不妙
Uh-oh.
烙饼还是香肠匹萨
Plain old cheese or delicious pepperoni?
不要啊
No!
哈 也许这就是
Huh, I guess there is something good.
普普通通的好处
About being plain.
剩最后一块不吃 可惜了
It'd be a shame to leave just one.
我害怕的就是这个
I was afraid of that.